<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
//
// This is the place for your statements. The maximum
// number of statements is theoretically unlimited, but
// less then 50 statements are advisable.
// If your are using German Umlauts and other special
// characters, make sure, that you save this XML-file
// as an UTF-8-document. White-space inbetween the
// nodes are ignored. Any white-space within the text-
// nodes, including leading or trailing whitespace and
// line breaks, is preserved.
//
// EXAMPLE
// Let's define some statements concerning FlashQ:
// Statement 1: FlashQ is very usefull.
// Statement 2: I prefer offline surveys.
// Statement 3: FlashQ is too complicated to configure.
//
// Each statement requires a seperate statement-node
// consisting out of an opening and a closing tag. The
// statement itself goes between this two tags.
// The unique statement id is saved as an
// attribute called 'id'. We have three exmaple
// statements and we need therefore three statement-
// nodes and one parent-node.
//
// <statements version="1.0" htmlparse="false">
//   <statement id="1">FlashQ is very usefull.</statement>
//   <statement id="2">I prefer offline surveys.</statement>
//   <statement id="3">FlashQ is too complicated to configure</statement>
// </statements>
//
// ===================================================
//
-->

<statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
  <statement id="AFF01">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for receiving status notifications and updates from third-party systems within channels (e.g., Jira, Git, InVision, Twitter).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF02">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for receiving real-time information from third-party systems within channels (e.g., critical errors, criticial user actions).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF03">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for receiving aggregated information from third-party systems within channels (e.g., lunch menus of nearby cafeterias,  generating meeting agenda).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF04">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for receiving metrics and key performance indicators from third-party systems within channels (e.g., velocities of scrum teams, stats about app reviews/ratings).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF05">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for setting and getting reminders within channels (e.g., reminder to clean the office or run a daily standup).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF06">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for setting and getting nudges/ triggers to action within channels (e.g., trigger employees to track working hours or fix unresolved issues).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF07">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for setting and getting nudges/ triggers to action and possibilities to resolve it within the channel (e.g., a message with buttons for employees to track working hours).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF08">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for capturing data in third-party systems from within channels (e.g., adding cards to Trello or Wunderlist).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF09">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for querying information from third-party systems within channels (e.g., query current sales, search on stackoverflow).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF10">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for invoking functions from third-party systems and make this invocation visible within channels (e.g., starting deployments, creating video conferences, asking questions on stackoverflow).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF11">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for adding gatekeepers that validate access to functions of third-party systems (e.g., ensuring four-eyes principle, requesting permission to deploy to production environment).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF12">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for having messages processed and enriched with additional information (e.g., enriching customer name with data from Salesforce).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF13">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for having messages processed and replaced (e.g., posting giphy or translated message).</statement>
  <statement id="AFF14">I perceive integrations into Slack, HipChat or similar as valuable for having messages processed and visually enriched with user interface elements (e.g., enriching poll with buttons and statistics).</statement>
  <statement id="CON01">I perceive the value of Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as limited, since most software at work is not open enough and has limited integrations with messenger.</statement>
  <statement id="CON02">I perceive the value of Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as limited, since my company constraints the usage of such messengers.</statement>
  <statement id="CON03">I perceive the value of Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as limited, since most of my work is not digital.</statement>
  <statement id="CON04">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations with third-party systems as constraining, since they lead to information overload.</statement>
  <statement id="CON05">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations with third-party systems as constraining, since I often already know the information from alternative sources (e.g., email notifications).</statement>
  <statement id="CON06">I perceive Slack apps and integrations with third-party systems as constraining, since I use these systems in my everyday work.</statement>
  <statement id="CON07">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as constraining, since the presented information lacks graphical and visual richness.</statement>
  <statement id="CON08">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as constraining, since they introduce process-orientation and reduce my autonomy.</statement>
  <statement id="CON09">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as constraining, since information is concealed after I sent the message (e.g., my individual values disappear, user identify is removed).</statement>
  <statement id="CON10">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as constraining, since I can achieve the same results with dedicated tools.</statement>
  <statement id="CON11">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as constraining due to a lack of rich user interface elements for entering data (e.g., it is annoying to pass numerous parameters with commands).</statement>
  <statement id="CON12">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as constraining due to a lack of configuration possibilities without programming customized integrations.</statement>
  <statement id="CON13">I perceive the value of Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as limited, since it is difficult to know how to use them.</statement>
  <statement id="CON14">I perceive Slack, HipChat or similar messenger integrations as constraining as it is more about playing and having fun than real value added.</statement>
</statements>
